<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DSA Spark</title>
    <link>https://dsaspark.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DSA Spark</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>CC-BY-SA 4.0</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dsaspark.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Points of Unity</title>
      <link>https://dsaspark.org/about/points-of-unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dsaspark.org/about/points-of-unity/</guid>
      <description>The Democratic Socialists of America has seen tremendous growth and development recently. Between the summer of 2016 and the summer of 2017, the organization has over quadrupled in size- with both newly-radicalized and longtime socialists joining and organizing into branches across the US. And while an organization going through such growth and transformation will inevitably go through growing pains and periods of internal strife, the rallying of tens of thousands of people to the broad cause of socialism is something to be celebrated and encouraged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Education</title>
      <link>https://dsaspark.org/about/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dsaspark.org/about/education/</guid>
      <description>Mike Macnair&amp;rsquo;s Revolutionary Strategy The free market triumphalism of the 1990s is over. Early 21st century capitalism looks like Karl Marx’s description: growing extremes of wealth and poverty, and irrepressible boom-bust cycles. But for the moment, rightwing religious and nationalist nostalgia politics is the main beneficiary of the opposition this has spawned. The political left remains in the shadow of its disastrous failures in the 20th century.
The centre-left - where it has not joined forces with the neoliberal right - clings to nationalist and bureaucratic-statist nostalgia for the social-democratic Cold War era.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight to Bring Socialism to the Labor Movement</title>
      <link>https://dsaspark.org/posts/merger-formula/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dsaspark.org/posts/merger-formula/</guid>
      <description>This article was originally posted by the Communist League of Tampa and has been reposted with permission.
William ‘Big Bill’ Haywood was an experienced union organizer and leader, as well as prominent member of the Socialist Party of America.
Jacobin previously published an issue completely devoted to exploring the history and future of socialist political organization in the United States. In a follow up article on January 28th, Editor Bhaskar Sunkara almost argues for working class political independence – for a working class political party separate from the Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Communism?</title>
      <link>https://dsaspark.org/posts/why-communism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dsaspark.org/posts/why-communism/</guid>
      <description>This article was originally posted by the Communist League of Tampa and has been reposted with permission.
I told a friend of my cousin that I was a communist. The response was a reflexive chuckle and an incredulous “Really? Why?” I think this sums up ‘communism’ for most people in the U.S. To American conservatives communism is the ideology of the state. The state infringes upon the rights of the individual, most importantly the right to private property, on behalf of some collectivity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>