<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Communism on DSA Spark</title>
    <link>https://dsaspark.org/tags/communism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Communism on DSA Spark</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>CC-BY-SA 4.0</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dsaspark.org/tags/communism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight to Bring Socialism to the Labor Movement</title>
      <link>https://dsaspark.org/posts/merger-formula/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dsaspark.org/posts/merger-formula/</guid>
      <description>This article was originally posted by the Communist League of Tampa and has been reposted with permission.
William ‘Big Bill’ Haywood was an experienced union organizer and leader, as well as prominent member of the Socialist Party of America.
Jacobin previously published an issue completely devoted to exploring the history and future of socialist political organization in the United States. In a follow up article on January 28th, Editor Bhaskar Sunkara almost argues for working class political independence – for a working class political party separate from the Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Communism?</title>
      <link>https://dsaspark.org/posts/why-communism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dsaspark.org/posts/why-communism/</guid>
      <description>This article was originally posted by the Communist League of Tampa and has been reposted with permission.
I told a friend of my cousin that I was a communist. The response was a reflexive chuckle and an incredulous “Really? Why?” I think this sums up ‘communism’ for most people in the U.S. To American conservatives communism is the ideology of the state. The state infringes upon the rights of the individual, most importantly the right to private property, on behalf of some collectivity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>